ICICI direct money app investing in
mutual funds
simple let's see how you can set up an
sip in a mutual fund scheme first select
a scheme and tap on invest
now select sip for regular monthly
Investments then enter the investment
amount that you wish to invest monthly
and pick the desired date on which the
amount will get
debited choose a payment source of your
choice
that's it you have successfully set up
your sip your sip will get triggered on
the date as selected by you you can view
the details of your ongoing sip from
manage Investments Under menu
options mutual fund Investments are
subject to Market risks read all scheme
related documents carefully